dreamtown.com 2018-12-28

# Dream Town Realty Terms of Use

### Terms of Use

www.dreamtown.com and ( "we," "us" and "our') is serious about its commitment to your privacy. This Privacy Policy covers the site www.dreamtown.com (the "Site"). We use the Site to provide you with information, resources, tools, products and services specific to the real estate industry and related markets, and to provide you with information about us and our advertisers, and our respective products and services. We want you to understand what kinds of information we gather about you, how this information is used and safeguarded, and how you can control its use.

By using the Site, you consent to the information practices described in this Privacy Policy. In conjunction with this Privacy Policy, you should also review our Terms of Use for a complete understanding of the rules governing the Site.

Information Collection

Personally Identifiable Information is information that can be used to locate you, contact you, or determine your specific identity. We collect Personally Identifiable Information from you in several ways:

  1. When you use the Site, we ask you for basic information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone, fax, user name and password and other basic contact information. In addition, if you choose to take advantage of some of our products and/or services, or to access certain of our tools or Site functionality, you may be asked to provide financial information. You can choose not to provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, but then you may not be able to fully take advantage of certain features of the Site and we may not be able to provide you with certain requested information, products and/or services.
  2. In addition to the collection of Personally Identifiable Information, we may also automatically track certain information about you as you visit and use the Site to help us to better understand how the Site is used and to better serve you. This information may include your computer?s IP address, the URLs and Site pages you have visited, the number of times you visit a particular Site page, what downloads and/or search queries you have made, how long you spent on particular sections of the Site and on the Site generally, and your browser type. This automatically gathered data includes information provided through the use of "cookies." A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookies to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it. We may set and access our own cookies on your computer. Information stored by us in cookies may be associated with your Personally Identifiable Information in order to identify you as a repeat visitor or customer of the Site, to maintain session information for logged in users, and to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of the Site.

Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information

In general, we will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent. There are, however, some limited circumstances in which we may need to disclose Personally Identifiable Information about a user:

  1. For products and services provided by the Site, the information you submit is used by us to provide the information, product or service you have requested. We may also share this information with others, but only to the extent necessary to fulfill your request or to facilitate your use of their services.
  2. We may employ other companies to perform supporting functions for the various tools, functionality, products and services offered through the Site on our behalf. We may need to share your Personally Identifiable Information to these companies. However, we will provide them with only that information necessary to perform their functions.
  3. For products and services offered to you jointly by us and a third party, your Personally Identifiable Information may be shared with or independently gathered by the third party. In these situations, we will only use your Personally Identifiable Information as outlined in this Privacy Policy, but the third party may use the information in different ways. You can tell when a product or service is offered by a third party, because a page of the Sites will be "co-branded" and will display the third party's logo and/or name along with our own, or you will be linked to the third party's site to complete the transaction. Please be aware that each company we do business with has its own policies regarding the use and protection of your information that may differ from those outlined in this Privacy Policy.
  4. Unless you specify that you would prefer not to hear from us, we may use the e-mail address you provide at the time of registration to contact you for promotional or other purposes. You may have these communications terminated at any time by opting out through your member profile on the Site, or by clicking on any ?unsubscribe? link contained in a promotional e-mail.
  5. We may reveal a user's identity (or whatever information we know about that individual) if we believe that user is harming or interfering with other users, anyone else, or violating (either intentionally or unintentionally) our Terms of Use or infringing any of our legal rights.
  6. We will reveal information, including Personally Identifiable Information, to the extent we reasonably believe it is required to do so by law. If we receive legal process calling for the disclosure of any of your Personally Identifiable Information we will, if permitted by law, endeavor to notify you via the e-mail address you supplied during registration within a reasonable amount of time before we respond to the request.
  7. We may transfer information we collect, including any Personally Identifiable Information, in connection with a sale of all or most of the assets of the company. Should your Personally Identifiable Information be transferred as the result of such sale, you will be notified via e-mail.
  8. Google is a third party vendor that uses cookies to serve our ads. The use of the DART cookie enables Google to serve ads to our users based on visits to our website and other sites on the Internet. If users would like to opt out of the use of the DART cookie, you can do so by visiting Google advertising privacy policies.

Security

We employ reasonable security methods intended to prevent unauthorized access to Personally Identifiable Information.

Your Personally Identifiable Information will be stored within a database that is located behind a firewall for added security. The server housing the database is physically protected at a secure, third party site.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we try to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Any transmission to the Site of Personally Identifiable Information and credit card information uses SSL encryption.

Other Web Sites

This Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

Children

The Site is not directed to children (persons under the age of 13), and we do not knowingly collect, either online or offline, personally identifiable information from children.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date first written above. From time to time, we may change our privacy policy. If we make any changes regarding disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, we'll send you an e-mail (or notify you by pop-up screen) prior to the date the modified policy takes effect. We will also post conspicuous notice of the new policy on our home page. Any new policy will have prospective effect only, meaning it will not apply to information previously gathered without your express consent.
